export const ReactNativeQuestions = [
  {
    question: 'Q1: What is React Native?',
    options: [
        'Framework for building web apps',
        'Programming language',
        'Framework for building mobile apps',
      'Database system',
    ],
    ans: 'Framework for building mobile apps',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q2: What is the difference between React and React Native?',
    options: [
        'React for mobile, React Native for web',
        'React for web, React Native for mobile',
      'No difference',
      'React for desktop, React Native for mobile',
    ],
    ans: 'React for web, React Native for mobile',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q3: What is JSX?',
    options: [
        'Programming language',
        'Database system',
        'File format',
        'Syntax extension for JavaScript',
    ],
    ans: 'Syntax extension for JavaScript',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q4: What is a "component" in React Native?',
    options: [
        'Navigation feature',
        'Reusable UI piece',
      'Styling function',
      'Programming language',
    ],
    ans: 'Reusable UI piece',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q5: What is "state" in React Native?',
    options: [
        'Built-in feature for handling user input',
        'Function used for styling',
        'Object that represents current data in a component',
      'Programming language',
    ],
    ans: 'Object that represents current data in a component',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q6: What is the difference between "props" and "state"?',
    options: [
        'State is immutable, props can change',
        'No difference',
        'Props are immutable, state can change',
      'Props and state cannot be used together',
    ],
    ans: 'Props are immutable, state can change',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q7: What is the purpose of "render()" in React Native?',
    options: [
        'Handles user input',
        'Returns the UI for a component',
      'Defines styles for a component',
      'Initializes state',
    ],
    ans: 'Returns the UI for a component',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q8: What is the purpose of "TouchableOpacity" in React Native?',
    options: [
        'Component for displaying images',
        'Component for displaying text',
        'Component for playing audio',
        'Component for handling touch events',
    ],
    ans: 'Component for handling touch events',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q9: What is the purpose of "StyleSheet" in React Native?',
    options: [
        'Defines data models for components',
        'Defines routes for navigation',
        'Defines styles for components',
      'Defines animations for components',
    ],
    ans: 'Defines styles for components',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q10: What is the purpose of "AsyncStorage" in React Native?',
    options: [
        'API for storing data locally',
        'API for making network requests',
        'API for playing audio',
        'API for handling touch events',
    ],
    ans: 'API for storing data locally',
  },
];
